我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但是我在时间中迷失了
But I became lost in time.
我的朋友们用尽了一切办法才把我救回来
It took everything in my friends' power to bring me back.
但我们的世界也因此出现了新的威胁
And in doing so, our world was opened up to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
每个热点代表一个人体
Each of these heat scans indicates a human body.
12个标记  12个超能力者
12 markers, 12 metas.
为什么有人要造出超能力者
Why would anyone wanna create metas?
我这是怎么了
What's happening to me?
显然这人是个公车超能力者
Clearly, this guy is a bus meta.
-让那些细胞拉伸  -就像弹性橡皮泥
- Stretch these cells. - Like silly putty.
就像弹性橡皮泥
Like silly putty.
我是弹性橡皮泥了
I'm silly putty?
让我和我的团队来训练你
Let my team and I train you.
你当初为什么调查贝洛斯市长
What made you look into Mayor Bellows?
是个客户  他的姓是迪沃
Oh, it was a client. Last name, DeVoe.
总之阿姆内特让你做什么你就做什么
You do what Amunet says for as long as she tells you.
告诉阿姆内特我要退出
Tell Amunet I'm done.
乔  我怀孕了
Joe, I'm pregnant.
那么想看看很酷的事情吗
Hey, you guys wanna see something really cool?
好啊  来吧
Sure, go for it.
伸展吧  拉尔夫
Stretch, Ralph.
伸展
Stretch.
很酷啊
That is pretty cool.
你确定找不到这个叫迪沃的家伙吗
Okay, look, a-are you sure we can't find this DeVoe guy?
我们被警告过  我们知道在未来某一天
I mean, we were warned. We had a heads-up that someday,
一个叫迪沃的人会成为我最大的敌人
someone named DeVoe would be one of my greatest foes.
另一个要考虑的事是
And the other thing to think about is,
你知道光是在这个州
do you know how many people there are
就有多少个叫迪沃的人吗
in this state alone with the name DeVoe?
-不知道  -好几千人
- No. - Thousands.
而且我们还不知道年龄
And we still don't have an age.
你的最大敌人不会是一个离着四个街区
Unless one of your greatest foes is the three-month-old
一个名叫威廉·迪沃的三个月大的婴儿吧
William DeVoe who lives four blocks from here.
我觉得我的敌人不会是婴儿
I don't think one of my greatest enemies is a baby.
邪恶杀手婴儿
Evil killer baby.
也有可能
Could happen.
你说得对
You're right.
费利西蒂
Yo, Felicity!
你怎么会来这
How'd you get in here?
我就这么走进来的  你们没有保安措施
I literally walked in here. You have--you have no security,
没有警报  什么防护都没有
you have no alarms, you have nothing on your door.
你们真的应该安点什么东西
You guys might wanna consider something, anything at all.
你带东西了
You came prepared.
从绿箭小队变成伴娘团
Well, yeah, Team Arrow to Team Bride, you know,
我对单身派对充满期待
very excited for that bachelorette party.
是的  被同性的人灌醉
Yep, getting inebriated with same gender
来庆祝一个古老的习俗
to celebrate an archaic institution?
珍贵无价
Priceless.
毕竟只结一次婚  所以
I mean, you only get married once, so...
其实
Well, actually,
这年头几乎每个人都会离婚
pretty much everyone gets divorced these days.
准确来说是55%的人  这是统计结果
55% to be exact, I mean, that's just statistics.
但是你和爱瑞丝不会的  你们俩
But not--not you and Iris. That would just--
你们俩绝对不会离婚的
that would never happen to you guys...
这是谁的脚
Whose feet are those?
拉尔夫·德比
That's Ralph Dibny.
我  我先去找女生们了
I'm gonna--I'm gonna go meet up with the ladies.
这
That...
闪 电 侠
第四季
第五集
机票
凯特琳·斯诺
你在这啊
Well, here you are.
你准备好参加
Okay, are you ready for the ladies' nights
最后一次女生之夜了吗
to end all ladies' nights?
她的意思是说  在一家很棒的餐厅了
And by that, she means a quiet, low-key dinner
吃一顿低调的晚餐
at a very classy restaurant.
是的  我就是这个意思
Yeah. That's exactly what I mean.
非常低调  非常安静
Super low-key, super quiet--
你喜欢粉色还是蓝色的羽毛披肩
do you want a pink or a blue feather boa?
爱瑞丝  我能不能不去了
Actually, Iris, if it's okay,
我今天晚上可能去不了了
I don't think I'm gonna make it tonight.
我觉得不太好
I'm just not feeling up to it.
怎么了
What?
你不舒服吗
Aren't you feeling OK?
不是的  我只是
No, I'm fine, I just...
总有些不顺心的时候
sometimes life catches up with you, you know?
是因为戴宝冠的不是你吗
It's 'cause you're not wearing the tiara.
戴上宝冠  她就改主意了
Put on the tiara. Everything will change. Oh!
-戴着宝冠  谢谢  -不客气
- Wearing the tiara, thank you. - You're welcome.
凯特琳  求你了  我们每天都在一起工作
Caitlin, please, come on, we work together every day
我们女生们从来没单独吃过饭
and we never get to do a dinner just us girls.
你一定要来
You have to come.
她说得对  就是吃顿饭  好吗
She's right. Just one dinner, please?
我会去的
Wouldn't miss it.
太不可思议了
This is so insane.
我不敢相信你又要当妈妈了
I can't believe you're gonna be a mom again.
你不是一直想要个弟弟或妹妹吗
I know, well, you always wanted a sibling.
播了七季的《神秘博士》  你终于想通了
And seven Doctor Whos later, you totally came through.
你喜欢看《神秘博士》吗  琼妮
You're a Doctor Who fan, Joanie?
他变成女的之后  我就喜欢上了
Well, ever since he became a lady, I am.
#女权主义
#Feminism.
单身派对
Bachelor party!
女生们都出去
Girls, get out.
我们该走了
Oh, that's our cue.
巴里  恭喜你结婚了
Hey, Barry, congrats on getting hitched.
谢谢  我都不知道你在城里
Thank you! I didn't realize you were in town.
我只是回来一个周末
Well, I just stopped by for the weekend.
太好了  很高兴见到你
Awesome. Good to see you.
我也是
You too.
玩得开心
Have a great time.
别玩得太疯
Don't get too crazy.
别喝酒
No drinking.
不  爱瑞丝答应过我今晚不会玩疯的
No, Iris promised me a totally chill night
就连我肚子里的小宝贝都没问题
that even my pregnant little booty can handle.
你应该跟我们一起去  亲爱的
You should come with us, sweetie.
爱瑞丝肯定不会介意的
You know, I'm sure Iris wouldn't mind.
不了  不去了
Uh, no, it's okay.
其实我有计划了
I, um, I actually have plans.
但是我会送你过去的
But I will drop you off.
好
Okay.
-玩得开心  -回见了  各位
- Have fun. - Later, guys.
拜
Bye!
我去关灯
Okay, I'll get the lights.
哈里去拿白兰地
Harry will get the brandy.
哈里  在你倒白兰地之前
Hey, Harry, before you pour the brandy,
一定要暖一暖杯子
make sure you warm the glasses.
-什么  -不是吧
- What? - For real?
没事
It's cool.
好了
Okay.
巴里·艾伦
Barry Allen.
准备好大开眼界了吗
Are you ready to have your mind blown?
这是巴里·艾伦
Meet Barry Allen.
在他遇见爱瑞丝·韦斯特之前
Before he met Iris West,
在他成为跨维度时间旅行极速者之前
before he became an interdimensional time-traveling speedster,
他是个像伊沃克人那样微胖的可爱小婴儿
he was an adorable baby boy with Ewok-level chub.
《星球大战6：绝地归来》中的人物
两个小脸蛋
Ugh, those cheeks.
西斯科  很不错
Cisco, this is great,
但你从哪拿到这些视频的
but where did you get these videos?
我就是个忍者  看看这部分
Man, I'm a ninja. Watch this part.
我忘了你们俩已经结婚了
Ah, I forgot you two got married.
你们俩以前年纪好小
Ah, you two were so young.
见鬼  我以前好年轻
Damn. I was so young.
先生们  我来了
Gentlemen, I have arrived.
-拉尔夫  -德比
- Ralph. - Dibny.
没想到你会来
Wasn't expecting you.
你说晚点见
You said see you later.
我猜这是超级英雄聚会
I assumed this was a superhero hangout
并且要测试我高度协调的侦查能力
and this was a test for my highly attuned detective abilities,
可事先声明  我完美通过了
which, for the record, nailed it.
好吧  或者
Okay, or...
我们没邀请你来
You weren't invited.
这家真是
Wow, this house is, uh...
-很破吗  -不是
- Bitchin'? - No.
好小  在街对面看还大一点
Small. Looks much bigger from the street.
这些都是什么鬼
What's all this crap?
这是我的单身派对
This is my bachelor party.
老天爷  你不是说笑
Oh, dear God, you're serious.
这纯爷们派对是你的单身派对
This weinerfest is your bachelor party.
这纯爷们派对的正打算在橡树酒店
This weinerfest is about to indulge in some
抽上好的雪茄和吃上好的牛排餐
very fine cigars and a very nice steak dinner at The Oak--
好了  别说了
Okay. Stop.
你会付五十块吃牛排餐吗
You're gonna pay $50 for a steak dinner?
-何乐而不为  -我知道有个地方
- Why not? - I know a place...
那里有自助牛排
Where you can get all-you-can-eat steak
鸡肉才4.99  还送纸巾
and chicken for $4.99 and they even throw in napkins.
我们走吧  姐妹们
Come on, ladies.
不去了  真的  拉尔夫
No, really, Ralph.
我们要留在这里  我们要...
We're gonna stay here, we're gonna go have--
不  瘦猴子
No, Slim Jim.
我坚持  你晚点可以谢谢我
I insist. You can thank me later.
这白兰地是要慢慢享用的
That was meant to be enjoyed.
我享用过了
I enjoyed it.
西斯科  别担心
Cisco, don't worry.
我们要去的地方  酒水任喝  而且景色
Where we're going, the drinks flow freely and the view is...
引人入胜
Ugh. Spectacular.
好高级
So fancy.
敬敬未来的艾伦夫人
Yeah. A toast to the future Mrs. Allen.
-韦斯特·艾伦  -韦斯特·艾伦
- West-Allen. - West-Allen.
虽然你和巴里的生活节奏也许很快
Although your life with Barry may be fast-paced,
我希望你们能好好享受这个特别的时刻
I hope you guys take the time to enjoy the special moments.
谢谢你们来
Aww, thank you guys for coming.
-对我真的很重要  -干杯
- It really means a lot. - Cheers.
好了  谁想喝我的香槟
Well, all right, who wants my champagne?
今晚我做出最疯狂的事就是点了两份甜品
Craziest thing I get to do tonight is order two desserts.
-我来喝  -对了
- I'll take it. - That's right.
爱瑞丝和我说你怀孕了  你怎么样
Iris told me you were pregnant. How's that going?
挺好的
Yeah, it's g-- it's good.
虽说这不在我的计划内
I mean, it wasn't exactly part of my plan,
但是我非常开心
but I just could not be happier.
我明白你的意思
I know exactly what you mean.
奥利弗和威廉怎么样
Oh, yeah, how is everything with Oliver and William?
我是不是听到你的未来响起了婚礼的钟声
Do I hear wedding bells ringing in your future?
不  上次我们筹备婚礼的时候
Oh, no, the last time we did anything that resembled a wedding,
奥利弗被箭伤到  所以...
Oliver got shot with an arrow, so...
你们叫了脱衣舞男来吗
Uh, did you girls order a stripper?
你怎么没告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
不然我就把单身好姐妹都叫来
I would've brought all my singles.
没  我
No, I...
妹子  你的喜好真吓人
Girl, you into some freaky stuff.
阿姆内特想见你
Amunet wants you.
凯特琳  你认识他吗
Uh, Caitlin, do you know him?
你要跟我走
You need to come with me.
我哪也不跟你去
I'm not going anywhere with you.
请告诉我这只是他表演的一部分
Please tell me that this is just part of his act.
如果是  那也太久了
If it is, it's taking too long.
脱衣服
Take it off!
真恶心
Gross!
我是叫你脱裤子  不是把眼珠拿下来
I meant take off your pants, not your eye!
天呐
Oh, my God.
退后  宝宝妈妈  交给我们
Stand back, baby mama, we got this.
我了个...
Holy...
请别这样
Please don't do this.
也不一定要这样
Didn't have to be this way.
什么
What?
我正希望能再见到你
I was hoping to see you again.
是吗
Really?
好让我再给你来一道疤吗
So I could give you another scar?
我讨厌粉红色
I hate pink.
是不是让你们倒吸一口气
Doesn't it just take your breath away?
女士们先生们  这是阿玉
Ladies and gentlemen, that is Jade.
先生们  欢迎来到金门乐
Gentlemen, I welcome you to The Golden Booty.
这里可没有什么可金的
There ain't nothing golden about any of this.
-才不  -你很喜欢吧  有什么想法
- Nope. - Came through for you. Right, man? What do you think?
我想咱们应该带些消毒洗手液来
I think I should've brought some hand sanitizer.
时刻准备着
Always come prepared.
太好了
Ohh, yes.
拉尔夫  这里的速度节奏和我不太合
Ralph, this isn't really my speed.
速度笑话  你可比这强多了  艾伦
Speed jokes? You're better than that, Allen.
我不是...
I wasn't...
你好呀  小拉夫
Hey, Ralphy.
迪士尼  你是这里的常客吗
Uh, Disney, you're a regular in this joint?
可不止那样
So much more than that.
女孩或许不是裸体
The girls may not be bottomless,
但对本人来说  薯条总是光的
but for yours truly, the French fries always are.
金门乐政策
Golden Booty policy.
出于对女士的尊重  不能碰  不能拍照
Out of respect for the ladies-no touching, no pictures,
不能录像  不能拿手机
no video, and no cell phones.
什么
What?
我需要喝一杯
I need a drink.
天  我希望我能喝醉
God, I wish I could have a drink.
兄弟  你以为我会让你失望吗
Bro, do you really think I'd let you down like that?
你的特殊调和物
Your special concoction.
保证能给予你温和  令人愉快的嗡嗡感
Guaranteed to give you that gentle, pleasant buzz
持续一整夜哦
all night long.
如果我们需要闪电侠呢
What if we need the Flash?
我自愿成为代理超级英雄
I volunteer to be designated superhero.
上吧  巴仔  你应得的
Go for it, Bar, you deserve it.
敬巴里和爱瑞丝
To Barry and Iris.
爱瑞丝来电
他们不接电话
They're not picking up.
刚才是怎么了
What the hell just happened?
那个美杜莎男是谁
Who was that Medusa man?
你知道这可不是西斯科认证的名字
You know that is not a Cisco-approved name.
不用在意那人是谁
Don't worry about who that was.
凯特琳穿衣服的品位和
Caitlin's taste in clothes is matched only by
她对男人的品位一样差
her taste in men-both terrible.
你怎么还是你  我以为凯特琳恢复了
Wait, how are you you? I thought Caitlin was cured.
凯特琳不应该对朋友隐藏秘密
Caitlin shouldn't be keeping secrets from her friend.
你们是朋友  对吧
You are friends, right?
是  我们当然是了
Yeah, of course we are.
你的朋友今晚准备出城呢
Your friend was going out of town tonight.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
因为她卷入了自己无法处理的事情中
Because she got herself into something she couldn't handle.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
去找出诺瓦克的老大然后杀了她
To find Norvock's boss and to kill her.
你为了这个换衣服是因为...
And you need a change of clothes for that because--
好吧  显然有人
Whoa, okay, apparently somebody
非常的开放
doesn't have boundary issues.
好吧  姑娘们
Uh, okay, girls,
我能在表层控制室和你们谈谈吗
can I talk to you in the Cortex?
咱们能先回溯一下吗
Can we take it back for a minute?
什么时候她的超能力会让她变超级坏蛋了
Since when did her superpowers make her a supervillain?
她不是个坏蛋  好吗
She is not a villain, okay?
我还记得前年被她绑架呢
I remember being kidnapped by her last year.
什么  好吧  是  但那是因为她当时
What? Okay, yes, but that is because she was
被萨维塔操纵了  而最后
being manipulated by Savitar, and in the end,
我们没有她是阻止不了萨维塔的
we wouldn't have been able to stop him without her.
你看  我知道她内心有善意
Look, I know that there is some good in there.
我明白
I get it.
理论上  凯特琳还是存在于
Technically, Caitlin is underneath
那一切之下的  但她依然危险
all of that somewhere, but she is still dangerous.
可她还是我们的朋友  好吗
And she is also our friend, okay?
我可不会就这么抛弃咱们的队友
I am not just gonna abandon our teammate.
好吧  我和你一起去
Fine. I'm coming with you.
不行  塞西尔  你怀孕了
No, Cecile, you're pregnant.
你要是在自己的婚前庆祝会上被杀了
And your father will kill me if you get killed
你的父亲可是会杀了我的
at your own bachelorette party.
这关系真复杂  这意味着我也要加入
That is some crazy logic and that means I'm in too.
真棒  婚前庆祝会快乐
Oh, great, happy bachelorette.
你们在那里说些什么呢
What are you all talking about?
没什么  你知道的
Oh, nothing, you know,
就是谈论下杀人是有多酷之类的
just talking about how cool it is to kill people and such.
不是故意指你
No pun intended.
这叫比较现实  女士们
It's been real, ladies.
我去用尖端科研实验室的卫星
I'm gonna use the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
追踪她的冷能信号
to track her cold signature.
好  我再去试着叫后援
Great, I'm gonna try and call for backup again.
我会试着记住那底下是凯特琳
And I'll remember that it's Caitlin under there.
爱瑞丝来电
你得停止这种行为
You gotta stop doing that.
我就是换点零钱
I'm just getting change for a five.
怎么  你以为我在偷钱吗
What? Did you think I was stealing?
这重点不是你手脚不干净  拉尔夫
It's not about your sticky fingers, Ralph,
是关于你在公开场合伸长的胳臂
it's about your stretchy arm outwardly displayed.
那么我是不是应该学学那边的谨慎队长
Oh, so I should be more like Captain Discreet over there.
我是闪电侠
I'm the Flash!
我那个婚前庆祝会灵药
I have slightly miscalculated
可能稍微猛了点
his bachelor elixir.
交给我吧
I got this one.
老兄
Hey, buddy.
-你感觉如何  -我感觉很棒
- How you feeling? - I feel good.
你可能得去走走醒酒了
You're gonna need to walk this off.
或者去跑一趟
Or run it off.
因为我是闪电侠
Because I'm the Flash.
咱们回座位那里去吧
Let's get you back to the table.
巴里
Barry?
你刚做了什么
What did you just do?
我就是去
I just went
吧台拿了点花生
and got peanuts from the bar.
你都没动
You didn't even move.
是吗
Or did I?
-喝吧  -我不用
- Drink up. - Oh, I'm good.
是红梅汁  毛茛属植物
Ah, it's cranberry juice, buttercup.
我刚才和善善聊了聊  不是她的真名
So I was talking to Charity-not her real name--
她告诉我舞女一个月挣的
she tells me the dancers here make more in a month
-比一般老师还多  -别说啦
- than an average teacher-- - Blah, blah, blah.
少说话  多看热舞
Less talky, more dancey.
下一位舞者  是茉莉花
Next dancer... It's Jasmine!
真火辣
Oh, yeah.
不是吧
Oh, hell no.
她看上去很像塞西尔的女儿
Hey, she looks like Cecile's daughter.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我以为你就喜欢揩油
I thought touching without permission is what you wanted.
我劝你让我过去  除非你想知道
I'd let me pass unless you wanna know what it feels like
眼球里液体晶化的感觉
when the liquid in your eyeballs crystallizes.
亲爱的  你在这里
Darling, you're here!
让她进来
Let her in!
Let her in, let her in.
阿姆内特
Amunet.
下一次你要找我  就自己过来
Next time you wanna talk, come yourself.
别派你的眼怪来袭击我
Don't send your eye-hole to attack me.
你去挑事了吗
Did you start a fight?
老实说  诺瓦克
Honestly, Norvock.
这就是为什么你只是我第三喜欢的小弟
That's why you're my third favorite henchman.
我总说什么来着
I mean, what do I always say?
永远别挑起你没法收场的争斗
Never start a fight you can't finish.
所以亲爱的  你才一直是我的最爱
And that, my dear, is why you are my favorite.
你懂得倾听
You listen.
显然  你不懂
Well, apparently, you don't.
我退出了  阿姆内特
I'm out, Amunet.
退出
Out?
退出什么
Out of what?
没选择了  还是疯了
Out of options? Out of your mind?
还是出柜
Out of the closet?
对于忧郁的女性而言  有很多种退出
There's just so many outs for the lady in blue.
你是要让我跳支舞吗
Are you asking me to dance?
你现在该知道  我从不求别人任何事
You should know by now I don't ask for anything.
我说了就直接去做
I tell, and I take.
过来
Now, come along.
我要给你看样让我俩
I want to show you something that could
都很富有的东西
make us both very rich.
你们觉得  他们会告诉我们
All right, do you think they're gonna be able to tell
我们和这里格格不入吗
that we don't exactly fit in here?
披披肩可是你的主意  所以不会
Well, it was your idea to wear boas, so no.
有男士们的消息吗
Have we heard from the guys yet?
没有  看
No. Look.
姑娘们  我们得靠自己了
Ladies, okay, we are on our own, okay?
来点爱意如何
How about a little love?
不不  不用了
No! No, no, no, no, no.
不用爱意
No. No love.
-订婚了  拜拜  -不要爱意
- Engaged. Okay, bye. - No love.
是我这么觉得  还是看上去
Is it just me, or does it seem like
这儿的人都买了那男人卖的药
everybody here already bought what that guy is selling?
姑娘们  呆这儿别动
Uh, ladies, stay here, okay?
我想我知道冰霜在哪儿了
I think I know where Frost is.
你有宠物了  恭喜
You got a pet. Congratulations.
我叫他哭泣者
I call him The Weeper.
我喜欢给超能力者命名
I love naming metas.
我认识个人也喜欢干这事
I know someone else like that.
三周前  这个年轻人变成了超能力者
Three weeks ago, this young man became a meta-human
而我得到了新宠产品来在我的交易网上卖
and I acquired my new favorite product to sell in my network.
你注意到了吗
Did you notice?
爱意
Love...
可是真的散播在了空气中呢
is quite literally in the air.
你知道为什么吗
Do you know why?
纯净
Pure.
他的眼泪是毒品吗
His tears are a drug?
他的眼泪  亲爱的
His tears, my dear...
是金矿
Are a gold mine.
中城只要尝一口
One taste and Central City
就会上瘾
will be hooked.
那你需要我干什么
Then why do you need me?
这还要问
Really?
如果我要售卖这么
Well, if I'm going to be selling something
珍贵的东西  当然需要靠山
quite valuable, I'm going to need protection.
你的老伙伴蛇眼不就是干这事的
That's what you've got good old snake-eye for.
这种生意
A deal like this
需要女人介入
requires a lady's touch.
在你这里就是  力量
I-in your case, strength,
我给你10%的分成
and I'll cut you in for 10%.
15%  而且我还加上了现在不因为
15%, and I throw in not killing you right now
你的背叛而杀了你  而这仅仅是因为
for your misguided rebellion. And that is only because
我现在肾里充满了宽恕  对吧
I've got forgiveness in my kidneys, right?
你想你是指心里吧
I think you meant heart.
不  我这里可没东西在跳动  妹妹
No, there's no beat beat in this chest, sister.
虽然玩"我是更厉害的坏蛋"很有趣
As much fun it is to play "I'm the bigger badass,"
但我玩腻了  像我说的...
I'm bored. And like I said...
我不干了
I'm done.
你知道在生意里大家都会犯的错是什么吗
Do you know what everyone's mistake in business is?
意识不到谁是房间里有话语权的人
Not realizing who has the power in the room.
姑娘们  我们先别用超能力了
Ladies, ladies, let's put the meta-abilities down.
抱歉  这小妞是谁
I'm sorry, who is this chick?
这小妞...
Oh, uh, this chick... Oh.
正想要尽力阻止一场超能力大战
Is trying to stop a meta-fight
以防毁了你迷人的俱乐部
from destroying your very enchanting club.
我们走吧
Let's go.
冰霜
Frost.
我们走
Let's go.
需要我阻止她吗
Should I stop her?
不用
No.
就让她以为她走得掉
Let her think she can walk away.
她没杀你算你走运  韦斯特
You're lucky she didn't kill you, West.
那是谁
Who was that?
阿姆内特·布莱克
That was Amunet Black.
地下市场的老板吗
Of the underground market?
我猜那小妞有犯罪记录
Oh, I'm guessing this chick has a criminal record.
对  她和超能力者黑市有关
Yeah, she's been linked to the meta-human black market
贩卖窃走的技术
selling stolen technology,
但我们一直无法拿下她
but we've never been able to nail her down.
你怎么认识她的
And how do you know her?
通过凯特琳  半年前
Through Caitlin. Six months ago,
凯特琳以为一切都在她的掌控之下
Caitlin thought she had everything under control.
这么厉害的反面角色可没法压制太久啊
Can't keep a good bad side down for long, am I right?
她感觉到我越来越强大
She felt me becoming much stronger.
她发现阿姆内特有一种技术
She found out that Amunet had some tech
能让她一直保持控制
that would let her stay in charge.
她走投无路  所以决定使用这项技术
She got desperate, so she decided to use it.
但这是有代价的
But it came with a price tag.
什么  什么代价
Which--which was?
做她的打手
Being her muscle.
你杀人了吗
Did you kill anyone?
有的人失去了手指脚趾  不过...
Some people lost their fingers and their toes, but...
没有  没死过人
no, no one died.
那你现在怎么在这儿
And how are you here now?
凯特琳睡着的时候  我就醒着
While Caitlin sleeps, I am awake.
我天  你就好像《无敌浩克》里那样...
Oh, my God! You're like The Incredible Hulk! That's--
我刚刚太得意忘形了
I said that with too much chutzpah.
-是的  -我调整下情绪
- Yeah. - Dialing it back.
对哭泣者  阿姆内特有什么计划
Look, what are Amunet's plans for The Weeper?
跟我没关系
Not my problem.
听着  他在那辆公交车上
Look, he was on that bus.
是我们创造了他  我们得救他
We helped create him. We need to save him.
不行  我得从阿姆内特那儿逃走
No. I need to leave and escape Amunet.
你就打算这么跑了
And you're just gonna run away?
听着  中城警局还没抓到她是有原因的
Listen, there's a reason the CCPD has not caught her.
你们这群傻蛋也才发现  过去这三年来
And that you idiots just realized
有个超级大罪犯一直就在
there's a major crime lord living
你们眼皮底下活动也是有原因的
under your noses for the past three years.
她太强大了  我们阻止不了她
She's too powerful. We can't stop her.
各位  我们对哭泣者和
Guys, we have a responsibility
这座城市都负有责任
to The Weeper and to the city.
你想让我们干什么
What do you suggest we do?
我们得在阿姆内特的计划实施以前
We need to rescue him before Amunet
把他救出来
does whatever she's planning, okay?
塞西尔  你去收集有关阿姆内特的信息
Cecile, you need to gather information on Amunet,
费利西蒂  你去找俱乐部的蓝图
and, Felicity, you need to pull up the blueprint to the club.
我们可以的
We got this.
我们是女强人
We're strong women.
没错
Yeah.
女权万岁
#Feminism.
金门乐
这不是你想的那样  乔
This isn't what you think, Joe.
那就好  因为我可是看见你
Good, 'cause I thought I saw you dancing
穿着亮片比基尼在那台上跳舞来着
on that stage in a gold sequin bikini.
我是在写一本有关女性经历的书
No, I'm writing a book on the female experience.
这书我愿意买
I'd buy that book.
动起来  姑娘们
Shake it, baby!
为什么你的女性经历就要包括
Why does your female experience
在金门乐跳舞这种事呢
include you dancing at The Golden Booty?
因为我们生活在一个
Because we live in a society
以男人视角为主导的世界里
that's dictated by the male gaze.
我想主导女权主义的叙事结构  好吗
I wanna control the narrative of feminism, okay?
我想让这世界看到一个强大  强壮的女人
I wanna show the world that a powerful, strong woman--
她想穿什么就穿什么
she can wear anything,
管它是比基尼还是衫裤套装
be it a bikini or a pantsuit.
或者什么都不穿  女权主义嘛
Or nothing. Feminism.
女权主义才不是这么回事
That's not how feminism works.
你就不能消停会儿
Will you cut it out?
琼妮基本上算是他的女儿
Joanie's practically his daughter.
闪电悲催侠  怎么一副哭丧脸
Sad Flash, why the face?
没事  我只是
Nothing, I just...
只是太爱吃鸡翅了
I just love chicken wings so much.
你要去哪儿
Where are you gonna go?
我认识个人能打开缺口送我去另一个地球
I know a guy who can breach me to another Earth.
从头来过  逃开阿姆内特
Start over. Escape Amunet.
成为我想成为的人
Be who I wanna be.
你是想成为冰霜杀手  是吧
And that's Killer Frost, right?
别天真了韦斯特  你阻止不了我的
Don't be cute, West. You can't stop me.
我也没打算阻止你
I wasn't planning on it.
我知道你可以杀了我
Look, I know you could kill me.
就跟你今晚本可以杀了阿姆内特
Just like you could've killed Amunet tonight
或是在六个月前杀了西斯科一样
or Cisco six months ago.
但你没有
But you didn't.
你的内心还存有善念
There is a part of you that is good.
还有良知
And decent.
你只是不知道该如何带着善念活下去
You just don't know how to accept it.
现在你自以为了解我了吗
You think you know me now?
没有
No.
但是我确实知道凯特琳害怕的时候是什么样子
But I do know what Caitlin looks like when she's scared.
而你现在的眼神跟她害怕时一模一样
And you have that same look in your eyes right now.
你只是害怕成为凯特琳
You're just as afraid of being Caitlin
正如凯特琳也害怕成为冰霜杀手
as Caitlin is of being Killer Frost.
要是你还想留着手
If you still wanna have a hand
戴上巴里的婚戒
for Barry to put a ring on,
就最好把手拿开
I suggest you move it.
有一个强大  强壮的女人
There's a strong, powerful woman
让我们两个又爱又怕
that we both love and fear
她就是你的母亲
and her name is your mother.
-她知道你在这儿吗  -当然不知道
- Does she know you work here? - Of course not.
她只会得出跟你一模一样的结论
She would just jump to all the same conclusions that you are.
琼妮  我和你妈妈只希望你能开心
Joanie, your mother and I just want you to be happy.
但我觉得你要扪心自问一下
But I think you need to ask yourself
这件事你为什么要瞒着她
why you're keeping this a secret from her.
乔
Joe?
为什么...
Why didn't...
露丝不在门板上给杰克让个地方呢
Rose make room for Jack on the door?
明明他俩都能躺开的
There was plenty of room for both of them.
西斯科  你这玩意儿的药劲什么时候能过去
Uh, Cisco, when does this gift of yours stop giving?
大哥  我不知道啊
Man, I don't know.
我本以为我们现在都回去看家庭电影了
I thought we'd be watching home movies right now.
再说一遍  不客气
Again, you are welcome.
你从我这儿偷了二十块钱吗  小拉夫
You steal $20 from me, Ralphy?
什么时候  我是说  我没偷
When? I mean... No.
你偷了
Yeah, you did.
我看见了
I saw it.
我等这一刻很久了  德比
I've been waiting a long time for this, Dibs.
你个混蛋
You monster!
都住手  我是警察
Everybody, stop! I'm a cop!
我是闪电侠
I'm the Flash!
你迟到了
You're late.
我来得刚刚好
I'm right on time.
怎么  在期待别的超能力者吗
What, were you expecting a different meta?
没人能逃出我的掌心  冰霜杀手
Nobody walks away from me, Frost.
你以为我会轻易地
Did you really think I was going to let you
就放过你吗
just breach into the sunset?
你欠我一条命
You owe me your life.
我的东西我自然要拿走
And I always take what I'm owed.
举起手来  夫人
Hands over your head, ma'am.
我的打扮哪里让你觉得
Is there any part of the way that I'm dressed
应该叫我夫人
that leads you to believe I want to be called ma'am?
血
Blood.
过会儿再收拾你  凯特琳
Kill you later, Caity.
我来帮你
Let me help you.
求你
Please.
好吧
Okay.
已经结痂了  你得用点力
It's already knotted, you just have to pull it tight.
谢谢
Thanks.
没事
Yeah.
发生了什么
What happened?
你不记得了吗
You don't remember?
当她控制身体的时候
When she's in control,
我都不太记得
I don't remember much of what happens.
她...  我有没有伤害别人
Did she-- I hurt anyone?
只是个小混混
Just that snake-eyed scumbag.
而且没有出人命
Didn't kill him, though.
看来解药...
So the cure, it...
没用
Didn't work.
还和以前一样
Not all the way.
所以你想今晚离开
Which is why you wanted to leave tonight?
所以你之前过了半年才回来
And why it took you six months to come back?
当西斯科说他能把巴里
When Cisco said he was gonna get Barry back
从神速力救回来的时候
from the Speed Force, I thought that
我想我可以回来
maybe I could come back and make up
弥补以前造成的伤害
for some of the pain that I caused,
但是她越来越强大了
but she's getting stronger.
我不应该回来的
I never should've come back.
不是这样的  凯特琳
That's not true, Caitlin.
你可以随时回到朋友身边
You can always come back to your friends.
你为什么不告诉我们
Why didn't you tell any of us?
我不知道该和谁说
I didn't know who to talk to.
你可以告诉我
Could've talked to me.
我是你的朋友  凯特琳
I'm your friend, Caitlin.
工作上的朋友
Work friend.
我觉得我们还不是
I mean, it's not like you and I have become besties
亲如姐妹的挚友
over the last few years.
没错  我们不是
Yeah, I guess we haven't.
杰里  老兄
Jerry, buddy,
法律规定我们不是可以打电话吗
we gonna get that phone call or what?
帮帮忙
Hey! Come on, man.
我知道你能听到
I know you can hear me.
我在这里
I'm right here. Hello!
好吧
Okay, great.
你还真是谁都认识
You just know everybody, don't you?
我来过这里几次
I've been in here a few times.
其实我能弄弯这些铁栏
You know, I could wiggle through these bars
带大家逃出去
and get us out of here.
也可以让手指变成钥匙  这样好一些
Maybe make my finger into a key, that'd be pretty sweet.
虽然开锁的时候会有点痛
A lot of pressure put on the index finger, though.
钢铁对肉躯
Iron versus flesh.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我觉得你应该立刻闭嘴
I think you should stop talking immediately.
再也不想喝酒了
I don't ever have to drink again.
喝多了的人都这么说
Words uttered by everybody who's ever had too many.
给
Here.
这次被逮到了吧
This was a bust?
单身派对
Bachelor party.
时有发生
Happens.
你怎么了
What's up with you?
整晚都心事重重
All night, you've seemed preoccupied.
我很担心
I'm worried.
担心什么
About what?
再次当一名父亲  我都快五十了  巴仔
Being a dad again. I'm almost 50, Bar.
当我看到西斯科做的你和爱瑞丝
When I saw that video Cisco made of you and Iris
小时候的视频时
when you were kids, I...
我感触很深
hit me like a ton of bricks.
我第一次当爸爸时还很年轻
I was--I was young the first time I did this.
而看到琼妮
And seeing Joanie?
抚养孩子不容易  巴仔
It's hard raising humans, Bar.
你会没事的
You'll be fine.
我担心你们三个
I barely get enough sleep as it is
担心地睡不着觉
worrying about you three.
尤其是沃利已经不在了
Especially with Wally being gone.
现在还要再添一个婴儿
Add to that a crazy baby schedule.
喂奶  哄孩子...
Feeding, the crying...
我真是怕得要命
I'm honestly scared to death.
乔  你独自一人抚养爱瑞丝
Joe, when you raised Iris, you were alone.
你独自一人抚养我
When you took me in, you were alone.
后来沃利来了  你也是独自一人
And, you know, when Wally showed up, you were alone.
你都是一个人
You did all that by yourself.
单亲父亲
Single parent.
没人能做得比你好
No one could've done a better job, no one.
现在你还有了伴侣
Now you've got a partner.
你有了一个家
You've got family.
你一直都在为我们付出
You've always been there for us when we've needed you,
现在轮到我们为你付出了
and now it's just our turn to do that for you.
我们会的
We will.
我知道你们会的
I know you will.
我来领那三个人
I'll take those three.
四个
Four.
这些碎片不只是水
These tears are more than just water.
接触到它的时候  里面的暗物质
When ingested, the dark matter inside it
会像精神药物一样影像人的大脑
alters the brain function like that of a psychoactive drug.
就像是鸦片吗
So it's like, what, an opioid?
像是春药
It's like a love drug.
会流泪
From tears.
如果这个传播开  中城就会面临
If this spreads, Central City's gonna have a massive
-巨大的毒品问题  -没错
- drug problem on its hands. - Oh, yeah.
我们要在那之前阻止阿姆内特
Okay, well, we need to stop Amunet
救了哭泣者
and save The Weeper before that happens.
我们要怎么找到她
How do we find her?
我不知道  她很聪明
I don't know. She's smart.
隔离外界  一直移动  从不留下痕迹
Off the grid, always on the move, never leaves a trail.
那她的超能力呢
Okay, well, what about her powers?
她控制的金属  你知道这什么吗
The metal that she controls. Do you know what it is?
一种亚力可合金
Some kind of alnico alloy.
你觉得能用我们的卫星追踪它吗
Do you think you could use our satellites to track it?
你是说给整个城市进行地质扫瞄
You mean run a geological scan of the city for
来找铝  镍和钴的小型特征
small-scale signatures of aluminum, nickel, and cobalt?
这还用问
Girl, please.
那  她往劳伦斯山去了
There. She's headed to Lawrence Hills.
那  那全是工业啊
That's--that's all industrial out there.
炼钢厂  码头和仓库
That's steel mills, docks, warehouses.
好吧  我们得阻止她
Okay, we need to stop her.
-好的  -各位我不能和你们一起去
- Okay. - Guys, I can't go with you.
如果我失控  就会成为负担
If I lose control, I could become a liability.
对不起  爱瑞丝  我不能去
I'm sorry, Iris, I can't go.
你不用去
You don't have to.
我们能行
We got this.
日语
女士们  你们状况如何
Ladies, what's your status?
我们到位了
We're in position.
我想你们会开心的
I think you'll be pleased.
这就是他
This is him?
好孩子
Good boy.
样本
Sample?
我来取代他
I'll take him.
-听我命令行动  -好
- On my count, we move. - Okay.
一  二
One, two--
三
Three.
我记得你
I remember you.
你不是酒吧里那个小妞吗
You are the chick from the bar?
不
Oh, no.
阿姆内特
Hey, Amunet.
这是你我之间的事
This is between you and me.
让我的朋友们走  我会回去为你工作
Let my friends go and I'll come back and work for you.
太迟了  凯特琳
It's-- it's too late for that, Caity.
你知不知道
Do you know why
为什么这么多年没人作证指认我吗
no one has ever testified against me over the years?
因为他们活不到那会儿
Well, it's because they're not alive to.
对不起
Sorry.
解决了他们
Take care of them.
不
No!
你好啊  冷冻人
Well, hello, Chilly.
我们得离开这
We gotta get out of here.
我以为我今天
And I thought I wasn't going
杀不了人呢
to be able to kill anyone today.
灭了他们
Kill them!
我觉得这撑不了太久
I don't think this is gonna hold much longer.
这是个钢铁厂
Well, this is a steel factory.
你移动钢板是用
And you move steel plates with--
磁铁
magnets.
很大  很大的磁铁
Really, really big magnets.
塞西尔  打开吊车
Cecile, turn the crane on.
什么  怎么弄
What? How?
应该在电路图里  就
Should be in the schematics, just--
就标注出来  然后打开它
just highlight it and turn it on.
好吧
Okay...
你和我本可以成为神的
You and I could have been gods.
我曾和一个神一起工作过
I used to work with a god.
忘了这事吧
Over it.
塞西尔  现在
Cecile, now!
磁铁激活
你没了武器  也没那么吓人嘛
Not so scary without your bling now, are ya, sister?
住手
Stop!
凯瑟琳  住手
Caitlin, stop.
我不是凯瑟琳
I'm not Caitlin.
如果她不死我就永远无法自由
And I'll never be free unless she dies.
不  恰恰相反
No, it's the opposite.
你现在自由了
You are free right now.
但如果你这么做  你就永远是个杀手
But if you do this, you will always be a killer.
冰霜杀手  凯瑟琳
Killer Frost, Caitlin--
你不用选择其一
you don't have to be one or the other.
你能决定自己是谁
You get to decide who you are.
滚出去
Get out of here.
现在你已经毁了我的事
You've ruined this for me today.
我发誓  不久我一定会摧毁你
And one day soon, I promise you I will ruin something for you.
等下
Hold on.
没事了
It's okay, okay?
我们要帮助你
We're gonna help you.
-离我远一点  -什
- Get away from me. - Wha--
警察就要到了
The police are on their way.
我们做到了  兄弟们  我们真的做到了
We did it, guys. We really did it.
应该是姐妹们
Actually, it's girls.
直到我的婚礼我都一直会头疼
I'm gonna have a headache now until my wedding day.
值得
Worth it.
再不提今晚发生的事  同意吗
Agree to never speak about what happened tonight?
-同意  -如果我必须的话
- Agreed. - If I have to.
什么
What?
我见你打了17个电话  还好吗
I saw you called 17 times, everything okay?
嗯  都还好
Oh, yeah, everything is fine.
你今晚怎么样
How was your night?
不错
Good.
祥和
Quiet.
-平静无事  -你的呢
- Uneventful. - Yours?
也没发生什么
Yeah, yeah, not much happened.
事实上  我们有些擦伤
You know what? We actually had a few scrapes.
说实话  我们也是
Honestly, so did we.
还流泪了
Some tears were involved.
没错  我们也是
Yeah, us too.
又哭  接着又吐
More crying. Then puking.
无法前往地球上最快乐的地方了
Lost access to the happiest place on Earth.
我相当确定没有什么可以使今晚变得更糟糕了
Pretty sure nothing could've made tonight any worse.
我好累
I'm so tired.
我真的好累  拜托有什么事能明天再说吗
I'm so tired, can we just do this tomorrow, please?
白发小妞
Chicks with white hair.
真性感
Hot.
冰霜杀手为什么会在这
Why is Killer Frost here?
伙计们
Guys...
她有话想跟你们说
she has something that she wants to tell you,
你们都该听一下
and you all should listen.
原来只是凯特琳
It's just Caitlin.
我可以解释这一切
I can explain everything.
乔
Hey, Joe.
你被捕的时候
When you got arrested,
我想着你会没事的  因为你是警察
I figured you'd be okay 'cause you're a cop,
不过仍然还是做得过分了
but still.
是的  我们都没事
Yeah, we're all fine.
你今晚过得如何
How was the rest of your night?
挺好的
It was fine.
乔  我要做我自己想做的事情
Joe, I'm gonna do what I want.
我知道  你是成年人了
I know. You're an adult.
我之前并非是想告诉你该怎么做
I was not trying to tell you what to do.
但说实话
But if I'm being honest,
我知道我今晚做得太过分了
I know that I took it too far tonight.
那你的女权主义研究呢
And what about your feminism research?
我现在依然相信我自己说过的一切
I still believe everything I was saying.
但我俩聊过之后  我意识到
But after we talked, I realized
那并不是我在那工作的原因
that's not why I'm working there.
所以我准备辞职
So I'm gonna quit.
你会把这事告诉妈妈吗
Are you gonna tell Mom?
这个秘密就轮不到我来说了
That's not my secret to tell.
但你妈妈爱你
But your mom loves you.
只要你愿意讲她随时愿意倾听你的心声
And she'll always listen if you let her.
刚买到我最喜欢的美食
Just got my first craving.
你们俩
Hi, you two.
今晚玩得如何
How was your night?
挺好的  一切正常  你呢
It was fine. Nothing happened. You?
一样
Same.
就是超级冷
Super chill.
我准备去睡觉了  不过
I'm gonna head to bed, but,
你想不想明早一起吃早饭顺便聊聊
do you wanna do breakfast in the morning and just talk?
当然可以  亲爱的  我很愿意
Yeah, sweetie, I'd like that.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night, guys. - Good night.
我要跟你说个事
I gotta tell you something.
我们俩的这个孩子
This kid of ours?
绝对不是个素食主义者
Definitely not a vegetarian.
我们俩的孩子
This kid of ours.
塞西尔  我得说
Cecile, I gotta tell you.
我从未想过我还可以再爱一次
I never thought I'd even have a second chance at love,
而你现在在我身边  你是我的一切
and here you are. You're my everything.
在这个奇迹之上  我们还有了这个孩子
To top that miracle, we're having this baby.
太令人兴奋了
It's exciting.
我可以说我有点怕吗
Is it okay to say that I'm scared?
你能跟我说这番话我太高兴了
I'm so glad that you told me that.
因为我也很害怕
'Cause I am terrified.
-真的吗  -是的  真的
- Really? - Yes. Really.
我原本以为我的人生
I-I thought that I'd finally hit this groove
事业以及和你在一起的这段感情已经圆满了
in my life and my career and with you,
而现在这个孩子改变了一切
and now this changes everything.
我们这个年纪最没想不到的就是居然有孩子了
The last thing I thought at our age, we'd be having a baby.
没错
I know.
是挺吓人的
It's scary.
但我觉得我们所要做的就是
But I figure pretty much all we gotta do
像我们彼此爱对方那样爱这个孩子
is love this baby as much as we love each other.
-那可真是满满的爱了  -没错
- That's a lot of love. - Yeah.
安静优雅到此为止了  对吗
So much for quiet and classy, right?
和你想像的单身派对是不太一样
Not exactly the bachelorette party you had in mind.
拯救这座城市倒并不是个夜生活的坏选择
Well, saving the city wasn't a bad way to spend the night.
但今晚最棒的部分就是这一整晚的时光
But the best part of the night was spending it
是和闪电侠队的女士们一起度过的
with the ladies of Team Flash.
没错
It was.
幸好我们没有差点被杀掉
When we weren't almost getting killed.
是的  我们应该多这样出来玩玩
Yeah, we should do it more often.
没错
We should.
当然了只是出来玩
The hanging out part,
除去差点被杀那部分
not the almost getting killed part.
乐意之至
I'd like that.
实际上  关于婚礼我想请你帮个忙
Actually, I wanted to ask you a favor about the wedding.
你想要一尊定制的冰雕吗
Oh, you want a custom ice sculpture?
不是
No.
我想问问你愿不愿意做我的伴娘
I wanted to know if you wanted to be my maid of honor.
我吗
Me?
是的  我俩不仅仅是工作上的伙伴
Yeah, we're more than work friends,
还一起经历了很多事情
and we've been through a lot together.
婚礼意味着新的开始  不是吗
Weddings are all about new beginnings, right?
所以你觉得如何
So what do you say?
你愿意当我的伴娘吗
You wanna stand up for me?
我愿意
I do.
不过这应是你的台词  对吗
I guess that's your line, though, right?
谢谢
Thank you.
-我好激动  -我知道
- I'm so excited. - I know.
我有伴娘裙吗
Do I have a bridesmaid's dress?
当然
Of course.
我废了这么大劲
I went to a lot of trouble...
创造了你
creating you.
可不能让你跑了
I can't have you running away.
在你完成你与生俱来的使命之前
Not until you've completed the task
可不能让你跑了
for which you were born.